Holding Our Own; Records apap365
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Holding Our Own Records
1981-2010
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap365
7.96 cubic ft.
This collection documents the day-to-day activities of Holding Our Own, an organization established to incite and support feminist social justice in New York's Capital Region.
Collection X
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Carmen Rau in 2016.
Historical Note
Established in 1982 and existing for nearly four decades, Holding Our Own supported feminist social justice. A multiracial, multicultural philanthropic foundation led by women of color, Holding Our Own, Inc. awarded grants to organizations and projects in New York's Capital Region which benefitted women. Special attention was given to grassroots organizations and those which represented women who faced bias or had limited access to traditional funding sources. This included funding of reading groups for children of color, a recreation project for women with AIDS/HIV, carpentry training for battered women, and a cooperative tutoring project involving a public housing tenant group and a local college. Holding Our Own also partnered with the Women's Building Project to fund and provide access to services and programs improving the quality of life for women and girls in the Albany area. When choosing organizations and programs to fund, Holding Our Own prioritized intersectional projects that served all women regardless of race, sexuality, age, ability, ethnicity, religion, education or class.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains meeting minutes, grant materials, award ceremony files, subject files, conference materials, administrative records, project reports, and other administrative files.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Women--New York (State)--Social conditions; Minutes; Files by subject; Grant proposals; Feminism--New York (State); Lesbian feminism--New York (State); Fundraising; Awards; Lesbian activists -- New York (State).; Social Activists; Nonprofit organizations; Women in nonprofit organizations; Albany, New York; Women; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Holding Our Own (Albany, N.Y.)
- 990 EZ and Charitable Organization Filings, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ABC Planning Associates, 1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Adirondykes, 1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Adirondykes, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ads, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Albany Actresses, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Albany Community Development Agency, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Albany County Domestic Violence Task Force, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Albany County Women's Building Project, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Albany Feminist Forum, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual Auction, 1996; 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Application and Guidelines, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Applications and Grant Review Materials, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Artist Support Services, 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Art Show Flyers, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Avoiding Date Rape, 1992 (Video-tape 1)
- Award Ceremony, 2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Awarded Grants, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Backup Historical Info, 1984; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Balance Sheets, 1988; 1981-2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Barbara Smith Award, 1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barbara Smith/Kitchen Table Press, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- BirthNet, 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Birth Project, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Black Woman Writer and Diaspora, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Board Agreements, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Board Agreements, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Board Committees, 2000; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Board Member Processing, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Board Members, 2000; 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Board Packet, 1982-1983; 1992; 1998-2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Board Search Committee, 1994-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Calendar Expansion and Increased Publicity, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Calendar Pages, 1985-1988; 1990; Undated (Flat-file 1)
- Calendar Pages, 1989 (Flat-file 2)
- Calendar Pages, 1990 (Flat-file 3)
- Capital Area Women's Caucus for Art, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Capital District March on Washington Lesbian Caucus, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Capital Region Association of Grantmakers, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Cash Flow Projections, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Catherine Winter Loan, 1981; 1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
- The Center for Alternative Dispute Resolution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Center for the Disabled, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Changemakers Grant, 2000-2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Charitable Contribution Rules, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Charitable Contribution Substantiation, 2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Cheryl Hopkins, 1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Chicago Foundation for Women, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Citizens Party, 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Claudia Brenner on Sally Jessey, Undated (Video-tape 2)
- Coming of Age E-mails, 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Coming of Age Lift Project, 2001; Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Committee for Anti-Racist Training, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Community Funding Board, 1984-1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Community Funding Board Grants and Agenda, 1985-1987; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Community Funding Board Guidelines, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Community Funding Board Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Conference Participants, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Conference Planning Committee: Mothers Courage, Lesbians Parenting, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Construction, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Contact Information, 1982-1984; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Contracts, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Coordinating Council, 2002; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Coordinating Council Agendas, 1990; 2000-2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Coordinating Council Lists, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Coordinating Council Minutes, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Coordinating Council Minutes, 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Coordinating Council Resumes, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with Rita Nolan, 1989-1992; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Council of Community Services, 1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Current Program, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Development Committee, 1990-1991; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Development Committee, 1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Development Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Development Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Dinner Party Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Donation Letters, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Donations, 2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Donor Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Donors, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Donors, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Donors, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
- "Don't Go To Your Room" and Other Affirmations of Empowerment for Women with Disabilities, Undated (Video-tape 3)
- Dvora Ziprin, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Educational TV and Film Inc., 1981; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Endorsements, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Every Women's Council Glens Falls, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Facing the Future's Fears: The Women's Peace Encampment, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Family Shelter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Films and Video, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Finance Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Finance Committee Development Retreat, 1991; 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Financial Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Financial Report for NEA, Kitchen Table, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Financial Statements, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Financial Workshop, 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Fleet Grant, 1983; 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Focus Groups, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Foundation Applications, 1989; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Friends of Auction, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Friends of Women's Studies, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Fulton County Coalition vs Domestic Violence, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Fundraising, 1994-1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Fundraising, 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Fundraising, 1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Fundraising Appeals, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Fundraising Articles, 1991; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Fundraising, Auction Programs, 1992; 1997-1999; 2001; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Fundraising Cycle Four, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Fundraising Letters, 1994-1995; 1997-1998; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Fundraising Party, 1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Fundraising Resources, 1990-1992; 1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Fundraising Workshops and Information, 1990-1991; 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Getting My Act Together, 1986; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Girls Inc., 2005 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Girls Night Out Caf, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Grand Opening, 1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Grant Application Form (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Grant Applications (1 of 2), 2002; 2008; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Grant Applications (2 of 2), 2002; 2008; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Grant Assistance Program Forms, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Grant Assistance Program and Past Loan Requests, 1983; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Grant Award Ceremony and Reception, 1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Grant Award Lists, 1983; 1987; 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Grant Awards, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Grant Contracts, 1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Grant Contracts, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Grant Contracts, 1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Grant Contracts, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Grant Contracts, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Grant Contracts, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Grant Cycle 3, 1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Grant Cycle Questions, 2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Grant Guidelines, 1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Grant Original Proposals, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Grant Participation, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Grant Proposals, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Grant Reception, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Grantee Info, Publicity, Reports, 1997; 1999; 2000-2001; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Grantees Contracts, 2008-2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Grants, 1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Grants, 1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Grants, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Grants Advisory Committee, 2002; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Grants Awards, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Grants Contract Forms, 1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Grants and Contributors, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Grants Meetings, 1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Grants Program, 1984; 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Grants Request, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Grassroots Fundraising Journal and Other Fundraising Resources, 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Guidelines and Applications, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Halloween Dance, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Harriet Tubman Holiday Initiative, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Health Conference, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Holding Our Own Agreement, 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- HOO Information, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Housekeeping: A Question of Love, Undated (Video-tape 4)
- Human Resources, 2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Human Resources Committee, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Human Resources Committee, 1999; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- The Institute for Research in History, 1983-1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Interfaith Center, 1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Investments Committee, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Jayne Williams "Slow Fat Triathlete", 2004; 2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Judith McDaniel Grant Assistance, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Judy Grahn Reading, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press, 1985-1986; 1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Knolls Action Project, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Leadership Committee, 1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Legal Conference, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Lesbian Connection, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Lesbian Connection, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Lesbian Connection, 2004-2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Lesbian and Gay Issues Working Group Funding Directory, 2005; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Lesbian Herstory Archives Newsletter, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Lesbian Nun Support Group, 1987; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Lesbian Safety Network, 1983; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Liaison Committee, 1990-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Lis Harvey: Human After All, 2000 (Cd 1)
- Loan Agreement Forms and Promissory Notes, 1985; Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Loan Committee, 1990-1992; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Loan Fund Guidelines, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Loans, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Loans: Holding Our Own, 1983; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Logo Stats, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Long Haul Press, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Los Angeles Women's Foundation Bylaws, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Maize Loan, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Massage Project, 2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Maureen Brady: Secret Settings, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Media, 1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Media, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Media, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Membership Info., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Michigan Women's Festival, 1982; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Michigan Women's Music Festival, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Monthly Record of Rents Received, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Monthly Record of Rents Received, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Mother Warriors Voice, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Motherhood Conference, 1985; Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Mother's Courage: Lesbian Mothers Conference, 1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
- National Conference of Puerto Rican Women, 1986-1987; 1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Networking Fair, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Networking Fair, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Networking Posters, 1999; 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- New Board Packet, 1995-1996; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
- New Paltz Women's Studies, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- New York Liberty, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- New York State Council of the Arts, 1981; 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- News Articles, 2005; 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Next Step Cross Country Race, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Nominating Committee, 1993-1997; 1999; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Non Violence Project, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Non Violence Project, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NYS Coalition Against Domestic Violence, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NYS Coalition Against Domestic Violence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- On the Line, 1984; Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- On the March Productions, 1984; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Original Grant Applications, 2002; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Original Grant Proposals, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Outreach Materials, 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Paid Bills, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Paid Bills, 2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Paine/Webber Financial Advisors, 2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Payroll, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Personnel Committee, 1990; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Phoenix, 1984; Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Phone Bank, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Phone Banking, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Planning Retreat, 1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Pledge Commitments, 2002; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Pledge Files, 1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Press, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Press Releases, 1998; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Prison Families of New York, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Program Committee, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Program Committee, 1993-1996; Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Program Committee, 2000; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Program Services Log and Info Correction Forms, 2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Programming Telephone Questionnaire, 1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Project Items, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Project Reports and Materials, 1982; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Project Reports and Materials, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Project Reports and Materials, 1999-2000; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Project Reports and Materials, 2000-2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Proposals Not Founded, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Proposals Not Founded, 1984; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Proposals Not Founded, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Proposals Not Funded, 1990; Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Public Relations and Fundraising Brochures, 2002; Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Publicity, 1988; 1994; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publicity, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Publicity, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Publicity Contacts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Rate it X Benefit, 1985-1988; 1991; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Receipts, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Receipts, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Redwood Records, 1981-1982; 1984; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Report on Women's Building, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Resist, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Review and Rating Forms, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Revised Applications, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Safe Shelter Saratoga, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Sample Proposals, 1985; Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Saratoga Women's Health Alliance, 1987; Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Schenectady YWCA, 1981; 1983-1985; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- SEFA Application, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- SEFA Application, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
- SEFA Application, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Self Defense: Women Teaching Women, Undated (Video-tape 5)
- Self Development/Homeless Women, 1993; 1997; Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Seneca Encampment, 1983-1987; Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Seneca Women's Peace Encampment, 1974; 1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- SEO Grant, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
- SEO Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- SEO Loan Program, 1985-1990; Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Siena College, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Siena College Women and Minority Program, 1983-1986; Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Sister to Sister, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Sister to Sister, 1999; Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Sister to Sister, 2000; Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Sister to Sister Conference, 1992; Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Sister to Sister Conference, 1996; Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Sister to Sister Grant Applications, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Sister to Sister Networking, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Soul Squad, 2005; Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Sound Ideas, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Sound Ideas Sample, Undated (Cassette 1)
- Spinsters Ink Publishing, 1984; Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Spring Benefit Dance, 1996; Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Spring Fundraiser, 1996; Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- State Employees Federated Appeal, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- State Employees Federated Fund, 1986-1987; 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Strategic Planning Committee, 1990-1993; Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- SUNY Albany Women's Studies Program, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- SUNYA Student, Afroamerican Studies, 1985; Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Talk Shows: Gay and Lesbian Issues, Undated (Video-tape 6)
- Tax Forms 990 and 497, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Tax Returns, 2002-2004; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Thank Yous, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Unity House Conference, 1984; Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
- U.S. Trust, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- U.S. Trust Co., Correspondence with Stephen Moody, 1982-1983; 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- U.S. Trust Correspondence, 1987; 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- U.S. Trust Income Tax Information Letter, 1989; 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- U.S. Trust Investment, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- U.S. Trust Investment, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
- U.S. Trust Investment, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
- U.S. Trust Investment, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- U.S. Trust Investment, 1994; Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
- U.S. Trust Investment, Income Tax Information Letters, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- U.S. Trust and Key Trust Statements, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Whole and Well: Women Creating Health Alternatives Conference, 1986 (Cassette 2)
- Who Lives Here, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Wiawaka Holiday House, 1998; Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
- WMHT Meeting, 1994; Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- WNBA, 1998; Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Women Centered News, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Women Confront the Roots of Violence, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Women Confront the Roots of Violence, 2002; Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Women Creating Change, 2002; Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Women in Theatre: Agnes Futterer, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Women Literature Critics and Writers, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Women Make History, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Women Make Movies, 1985-1986; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Women of Color Institute, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Women of Power, 1984-1985; 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Women of the Arts: Music, 1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Women's Building, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Women's Building Accountant, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Women's Building Calendars, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Women's Building Financial Reports, 1988; 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Women's Building General Contractor, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Women's Building/Holding Our Own Proposal, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Women's Building Membership, 1999; Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Women's Building Organizations, 1985; Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Women's Building Planning and Retreat, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- The Women's Building Project, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Women's Building Project Correspondence, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Women's Building Project Meeting Minutes, 1984; Undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Women's Building Project No. 2, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Women's Building Project: Quarterly Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Women's Building Project Quarterly Report, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Women's Building Transition, 2004; Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Women's Building Transition Team Reports, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Women's Building Website, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Women's Caucus of Non Violence, 1986; Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Women's Educational Media, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Women's Encampment Ad Hoc Group, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Women's Health Group, 1984; Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Women's Interart Center, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Women's Movement, 1988; Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Women's Music and Video, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)